<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Failing Up]]></title><description><![CDATA[A little blog.]]></description><link>https://agoudarzi.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 22:49:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Rocky New Start]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am officially a paid prop trader! This amazing news is one that I have been working towards for a long time now, but it seems every bit of…]]></description><link>https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-30-rocky-new-start/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-30-rocky-new-start/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I am officially a paid prop trader! This amazing news is one that I have been working towards for a long time now, but it seems every bit of great news comes along with it, some bad news. That almost puts a wet blanket on it.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The platform I have been working on and honing my skills in because of this prop firm telling me to use it, is now telling me they no longer support this platform I am so used to and love. It’s definitely a recipie for faliure, but currently exploreing other optiions like (Overcharts)[overcharts.com]. While there isn’t any real documemtation on them and from other users, then their own official youtube channel. Very strange…
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Well, always have to roll with the punches and keep on trucking.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[So Many Things]]></title><description><![CDATA[Every loser gotta win and every winner gotta lose someday - J. Cole When it rains, it absolutely pours. A million things tend to come up all…]]></description><link>https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-29-so-many-things/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-29-so-many-things/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Every loser gotta win and every winner gotta lose someday&lt;/em&gt; - J. Cole&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it rains, it absolutely pours. A million things tend to come up all at once for some strange reason. I am currently working on 3 open projects on top of my day job. Trying to keep up with this blog and it has been a success.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tumultuous Markets]]></title><description><![CDATA[I was born to make mistakes, not to fake perfection - Drake
  Yesterday was my first offical day as a professional prop trader. I was given…]]></description><link>https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-28-tumultuous-markets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-28-tumultuous-markets/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I was born to make mistakes, not to fake perfection&lt;/em&gt; - Drake
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Yesterday was my first offical day as a professional prop trader. I was given my credentials at around 3:00 pm EST and decided I wanted to trade right away. In my limited time of day trading the financial markets, I already know in the back of my head this was a bad idea and continued anyway and ended up being down $1500.00 in a 20 minute period, which is pretty comical.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
I made that money back and more during the New York open today, while I stuck to my systems and was patient. It always sucks to start off on the wrong foot, even though it can be easily amended. Money is not really the issue here, it’s more emotional than anything else. Which I think can be applied to really every day life, including entrepeneurship and being a bootstrap solo developer. The emotional drain that goes into pushing any product to the finish line, or continually force yourself to work on something can be huge. It’s important to understand how your emotions work. Everyone is different of course, but what I understand from learning and being a 3d party observer to my emotions, is that I need a solid system that essentially turns me into a robot.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Robots blindly do what the instructions given to them are, with no if’s or but’s. Building my system is essentially allowed me to act in a similar way, because I know it works. Deviation from this robot-like behavior results in less than great performance, as shown by my trading yesterday, or start-ups I have pursued that didn’t cross the finish line.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Anyway, your portfolio really took a beating today, but because of my system, I made a killing… Which my robot system tells me to completely forget about to attach any emotion to this day, that will hinder future performance, as cocki-ness is just as/or way more dangerous and one who can’t pull the trigger&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weekends Don't Count]]></title><description><![CDATA[A gem cannot be polished without friction, nor a man perfected without trials. -Seneca
  So I failed up make an update yesterday which was a…]]></description><link>https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-27-weekends-dont-count/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-27-weekends-dont-count/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A gem cannot be polished without friction, nor a man perfected without trials.&lt;/em&gt; -Seneca
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
So I failed up make an update yesterday which was a Sunday. If I am being honest, I was a bit too hungover to do much of anything other than lay in front of the TV and veg out. Your body quickly loses it’s ability to deal with hangovers after 30, and what would normally be taken care of by a little brunch and hair of the dog, turns into a full day wasted.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Anyway, the streak continues! After my brief heitaus, I decided I wanted to pursue an idea with a friend of mine in the real estate space. I am placing my workout app on hold at the moment. Whilst I sit and re-think the database structure for it. Long story short, I need to solve an issue revolving around creating a custom workout for x number of days and being able to log those sessions in a good way. Right now, I am mentally stuck on it, which makes me really discouraged from working on it. I am hoping to clear my head on it and have some random Eureka moment in the shower. I might also go the right of making mocks and seeing if I could validate it by emails. We shall see, but I am pretty close on the MVP, so I might as well try and finish it.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Onto the real estate application. Doing my research I am starting to see how antiquated the entire system is, how Redfin is doing their work with homes, and it’s all pretty wild to me how ripe this market is for changing. Especially since this is such huge industry, why haven’t more tech companies come out of here? The app itself is pretty simple and already have market validation via the Real Estate Agent friend of mine. I have pretty good hopes for this, as we already have a few clients lined up.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Almost There]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fires feeds on obstacles. - Marcus Aurelius
  This is the last Saturday for the month of September 2021. It is a beautiful fall day in the…]]></description><link>https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-25-almost-there/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-25-almost-there/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fires feeds on obstacles.&lt;/em&gt; - Marcus Aurelius
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This is the last Saturday for the month of September 2021. It is a beautiful fall day in the Washington DC area, and yet, here I am, continuing this relenentless update on the blog.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
I always hoped, but never Imagined my streak would be this great. You know something is starting to become a habit, when you start to feel bad when you don’t do that activity. Wether it be going to the gym or writing in a blog. Habit building requires a system and a knowledge of one-self. Not trying to hype myself as all knowing, just years of failures has led to me understanding what doesn’t work for me and that is infinitely more important that what I know works for me.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Baby steps trying to get this page back up on &lt;a href=&quot;https://agoudarzi.com&quot;&gt;agoudarzi.com&lt;/a&gt;. Deleteing old repos, trying to get it hosted properly on github pages. Shout out to github and github pages for allowing free hosting on this site, with what appears to be unlimited storage? (might need to figure out how to abusive this). Anyone with a few hours of time to kill and really no knowledge of coding code make their own website at the cost of a little time and the price of the domain itself. This domain cost me around $1.98 originally several years ago at purchase and 2.99 per year to keep. So really just the price of a coffee a year.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Might start making some guides on here&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Staying Motivated]]></title><description><![CDATA[Staying Motivated I can’t believe how long I have lasted already, breaking my last record by leaps and bounds. This is further reinforcing…]]></description><link>https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-24-staying-motivated/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-24-staying-motivated/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Staying Motivated&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can’t believe how long I have lasted already, breaking my last record by leaps and bounds. This is further reinforcing my system of just writing out, whatever it may be, to reduce as much friction as possible. Still maybe too early to tell, but this has already a great feeling to keep this up, dispite not really saying much.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In the process of resurecting this blog was figuring out how Gatsby worked and how I was able to get this loaded onto github pages. What I was able to do a couple years ago, is now a complete mystery to me.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
While I couldn’t actually figure out the steps I took and I didn’t leave myself a great paper trail to follow and I definitely broke my whole page trying to overwrite the existing repo, I am still writing on this broken site. What I normally would have done in the past, was throw my hands up and completely abandon this endeavor, but my system has prevailed of taking the smallest, easiest steps to reduce friction. While this site not being up is a HUGE source of friction, writing for the sake of writing (whatever that may be) is still going on.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
While trying to navigate around Gatsby, I sometimes wonder why I have the need to make things way more difficult. This blog could really be written in one single &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;.html&lt;/code&gt; file, but instead I am using another JS framework to make a bunch of static pages. Where is the fun in that though?
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In trying to bootstrap projects (or even this blog), I have come to terms of trying to simplify as much as possible. This was/is a lot harder for me than anything else, but as I was talking about reducing friction before, &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;simplfying -= friction&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[On Fire]]></title><description><![CDATA[On Fire This is already a great start, I can’t believe I have actually written in this blog 3 days in a row, my longest ever! Although I don…]]></description><link>https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-23-on-fire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-23-on-fire/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;On Fire&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is already a great start, I can’t believe I have actually written in this blog 3 days in a row, my longest ever! Although I don’t want to jynx it, I feel this system I attempted is most sustainable way to get this going.
&lt;br&gt;
Half the battle is making it so easy for you to do it, while removing any friction surrounding that behavior. Although I might be speaking too soon…
&lt;br&gt;
Anyway, aside from my little celebration (hopefully not too pre-emptive), I wanted to use this blog as a documation of my journey into true entrepeneurship and show how anyone can really do anything. I believe a lot of success is due to luck, but placing yourself in a position to be lucky is the most important part. I have several failed start-ups already under my belt, so hopefully luck will hit soon, but will continue on none-the-less.
&lt;br&gt;
I got my first contract with a big festival in the DC area for my digital immersive marketing company, excited and dreading the amount of work that will go into this. A win is a win so i’ll take it.
&lt;br&gt;
I should probably get a spell checker in markdown, but for the time being, enjoy my spelling mistakes as I remove any friction from writing here.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Big Plans]]></title><description><![CDATA[Big Plans I am already on a great streak with this blog, with the highest back-to-back streak of 2 days. I already think that less stress on…]]></description><link>https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-22-another-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-22-another-post/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Big Plans&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am already on a great streak with this blog, with the highest back-to-back streak of 2 days. I already think that less stress on editing and making this the most visually appealing blog, has already given way to the start of a beautiful system of writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One main purpose of this blog is to be a psudeo-jounal for documenting my journey into entrepeneurship. I like to work on software and even like to consider myself a “maker”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to really pursue creating my software unicorn, I really need a good cash flow. Logically that has led me down the road of day trading, where I have been extremely focused on speculating on Index futures (ES, NQ, for those in the know). Trading allows me the flexibility to generate revenue, while I try my hand at multiple SaaS projects, without the added stress of trying to feed myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently I am a software engineer at a large firm, living pretty comfortably, but soon I will need to really push out, in order to really see if I can live this lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[First Post of a new blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[Starting over So I have probably had this “blog” for 5 years now and many failed attempts at keeping it up after a week. I think I may have…]]></description><link>https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-21-first-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agoudarzi.com/2021/2021-09-21-first-post/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Starting over&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I have probably had this “blog” for 5 years now and many failed attempts at keeping it up after a week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I may have figured out how I can actually continue blogging and making it more of a habit. I think I may have been trying too hard to make it look like the amazingly ornate blogs that I often stumbleupon, from designers and engineers I could never hold a candle to. I think this has been taking out the fun in just writing and makes me focus on the failure of my asthetics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So in order to test my hypothesis, I am going to strip it down and keep it as simple as possible. No new shiny tech stack here. Simply what I use in my day to day and what I am the most efficient working in. With the exception of Gatsby, I live on React and Typescript. I already lied, GraphQL is needed to use Gatsby and I am not getting fancy with it, as I think that could be a bump in the road on my journey to making this stick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wish me luck!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>